JULY 12TH (MON) 5:05 PM
Yoshikage… My darling boy…
Where are you?
You must be in hiding, you must've
changed your face, even your name.
My poor son…
I'll make sure they pay dearly…
Right. We need to look further into
the recent missing-person cases.
That's including runaway cases.
Isn't Kira in hiding…
Do you really think he'd continue
on his murdering spree?
Serial killers like him
can't just brush aside
their murderous impulses.
He will kill again.
I wonder if wait and watch
really is the best way to go…
We haven't found a single clue
leading us to Kira.
I've been wondering the same.
But Jotaro did say…
If he finds something,
we spring to action.
Until then, we should go back
to being ordinary students,
according to him.
I'd rather hunt down that bastard
Kira than hit the books.
We almost got him that one time,
it'll be a one-two knockout.
KISARA DRUG
Yes. And since I'm repairing
the fire damage,
I'd like to do some
renovations, too.
That bastard!
He's snapping pictures of people
in search of my son!
I suppose I should
have an estimate.
That numbnut Jotaro
and his fellow Stand users
think they can lay down the law…
I will annhiliate these parasites…
I will give life
to new Stand users…
Hm?
That's…
I know that's him!
Altered appearances cannot
weaken the bond of father and son.
I could never mistake
my son for another!
I've found you, Yoshikage…
I'll find the answer…
I'll identify
this imposter of a dad
It can't be…
At this rate,
those Stand users will…
Never!
It stops now!
With every fiber of my being,
I will protect Yoshikage!
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
JULY 15TH (THURS) 7:50 AM
See ya later.
EPISODE 31
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 1
I'm gonna be late…
And I'm class monitor today!
JULY 15TH (THURS), 8:02 AM
I'm exhausted…
I stayed up way too late.
I slept like a rock.
Feeling fit as a fiddle.
Look, Josuke.
Binoculars.
Someone dropped their binoculars.
Well it doesn't take much
to capture your attention.
Gross. Don't pick them up.
What? Gross?
I assure you I am not gross!
Hi, Josuke and Okuyasu.
You again? Don't freak us out
like that, Mikitaka.
My heart can't take
shock like that.
Well, I wouldn't go so far as to…
Easy there. It's not a compliment!
Oh yeah, that's right…
You have perfect timing.
There's something I want you
to come clean on right now.
That whole bit about being
an alien was a lie, right?
You're just a Stand user
who's convinced himself
he's an alien, aren't you?
Quit screwing with us
and be real, dammit!
I have always been real with you.
I am an alien.
Why are you suddenly talking
like some weirdo?
Okay, fine.
Just what are you doing out here
transforming into
a pair of binoculars?
Oh, yes.
I want you two to see something,
hence my waiting here for you.
That?
That… That transmission tower
to be exact.
Transmission tower?
Well, it's not really
a transmission tower anymore.
Without its power lines,
it's more a remnant of the past.
When redevelopment
really took off in Morioh,
most power lines
were moved underground.
What's all this about anyway?
Is that what you're using
to communicate with other planets?
Smoke is wafting up from around
the center of the tower, yes?
Huh?
Y-You're right…
Have a closer look please.
H-Hey, look, it's a kettle!
What? Way up in some tower?!
That's like 20 meters up!
No, a little higher.
Could you please look
about 5 meters above?
What the heck?
L-Let me take a look.
There! Now I see him!
I see a guy!
- He's cooking something!
- What?! Let me see!
That tower… it must be his home.
He looks like he spends
his whole life up there!
He's fishing from the river,
he's even got cucumbers growing.
Clever bastard!
I get it! It's like
a self-sufficient home.
This world has no shortages
of curious individuals, does it.
Look out!
H-He's…
It's a new Stand user!
Yeah! He was definitely flying!
But what's a Stand user
doing living up there?
It appears that man
calls for a closer look.
Well what do we have here…
They've finally arrived.
I wonder whether
I caught their interest?
Don't be shy.
It's been a while since I've
indulged in a little chit chat.
Look. It looks like
he's noticed us, too.
Wanna go look?
Yeah, but play it safe.
We still don't know
whether that Stand user
wants to help or
beat the shit out of us.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:05 AM
Huh? Can I help you?
I'm sorry I kinda have to
get going, so…
Huh? Huh?!
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:11 AM
This thing looks a lot bigger
up close, huh…
You can stop right there, fellas!
I warn you, don't get any closer.
Huh?
I'd move back if I were you.
I just answered the call of nature,
and if you don't stand down,
you won't be happy.
I'm not really following.
D-Don't tell me this is…
Don't say I didn't warn you.
That there is my manure!
Eww, gross!
Gross? That's impolite!
I designed this thing so that
it'd distribute the fertilizer
to all the plants below!
I'm all about zero waste you know.
On the right are
Asiatic day flowers,
mountain asparagus, and watercress.
They're all completely edible!
And with all these plants around,
catching nibbling rabbits
is a cinch,
so I've got the best
of both worlds.
So you really are living up there?
Doesn't this tower belong to
some electric company?
What are you talking about?
I paid for this house
with my own money.
I bought this abandoned tower
for 100,000 yen
and turned it into my dream
self-sufficient house!
Bought?
For 100,000 yen?
That's right, a paltry 100,000 yen.
Since I support myself, I'm not
stuck working for some company.
I don't even have to
leave the house,
and I get all the exercise
I ever need.
Just get a load of
this amazing view.
Huh? W-Wait a minute.
You don't even have to leave?
Just how long have you
been living here?
Let's see…
I suppose about three years now.
Th…
Three years?!
I probably haven't even touched
terra firm a in about a month.
H-Hey, Josuke.
Who knew such a freaking idiot
was here right under
our noses in Morioh.
This guy is just
your ordinary nutcase.
He doesn't wanna hurt us.
No way he's gonna
try and attack us.
You're right…
I guess, for now, heading back
and reporting to Jotaro
is the best option.
Then again…
Something just doesn't feel right…
JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:15 AM
What's he doing?
I suppose children are known
to take videos, too…
But he's clearly hiding
behind that pillar,
like he's up to
the same thing I am.
He's following someone
and capturing their every move…
Could his target be
in this picture?
HAYATO KAWAJIRI
"Hayato Kawajiri," huh…
Something's unusual…
about this kid.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 7:33 AM
I'm home.
SILENCE
Well that's weird.
Josuke, you still haven't
left for school?
Josuke!
God I'm starving.
Josuke, that ungrateful…
He doesn't give a shit
about anybody else!
He takes a giant bite out
of my favorite Kamakura Custar
and plops it back in the fridge
like it never happened?!
There's supposed to be two
in here anyway.
He freak in pisses me off.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:14 AM
Hey, something fell out of
your pocket.
Is that a photograph?
Would you mind skedaddling?
Don't worry about picking it up.
I'll get it later.
It looks like a plain old Polaroid.
What's he getting
all worked up for?
It's fine! Just leave!
What?! You're that…
Hey! J-J-Josuke!
You're Kira's old man!
I should've known that bastard
of a ghost dad was behind this!
So you've finally stepped
into my abode. I've been waiting.
Tell someone to come in,
and they get nervous and refuse.
Tell them the opposite,
and they get pissed and enter.
At long last you've entered
into Superfly, Josuke Higashikata!
W-What?!
Well done, Toyohiro Kanedaichi!
You've ensnared that fool Josuke
into Superfly!
Kudos, friend, kudos!
I don't like the looks of this!
Shit… Come back, Josuke!
No, Kira's dad is right there!
He's got the arrow!
You bastard!
You little—
What?!
Once someone steps into
the tower's realm,
it won't spit them out until
its next victim steps in.
If they try to force their way out,
they simply become
a part of the tower.
That's my Stand, Superfly!
We got ya good, Josuke Higashikata!
Keep him in your clutches,
Toyohiro Kanedaichi!
Josuke!
SUPERFLY
Damn it…
Now I did mention it is my Stand,
but Superfly isn't exactly
under my control.
It pretty much does its own thing.
Now that you guys are here,
I can finally take off.
I've been trapped by Superfly
this whole time.
Well, take good care of
the place for me!
Sly sonuvabitch!
So he's in cahoots with
the ghost photograph guy.
Mr. Okuyasu, is there any way
I can be of assistance?
You'll just get hurt,
so stay out of it.
Your job's done.
Now if you could transform into
some dynamite
instead of dice or binoculars,
we might have something
to work with.
That would be impossible.
I can't transform into objects
more powerful than myself,
and explosives,
as well as intricate mechanisms,
are off limits.
But there must be
something I can do.
Shut up.
I already told you there's not
a damn thing you can do.
Leave the aggressive shit to us.
That asshole thinks
he's trapped his prey
while making some amazing escape,
but he clearly doesn't know
who we are.
Hey. You gonna go for it, Okuyasu?
Ready as you are, pal.
This tower's got nothing on us.
Let's bust it up, Josuke!
You know it. Busting out of here
will be a snap!
Whoa there!
The heck?
How'd they get so strong?!
This thing's pretty damn solid.
As long as we keep hitting it,
this thing should snap in two.
And look.
He's about to come crashing down.
Y-You knuckle-heads!
Think you can scare me, huh?
I thought you'd pull
something like that.
Guess you haven't noticed.
This tower has absorbed
your powers,
and redistributed the force
over its entire structure.
Huh? What the hell is
that jackass blathering about?
Josuke, hang tight, I'll have you
out of there in no time!
It's gloves off!
Hold it, Okuyasu. Listen for a sec.
This isn't normal.
What's that weird sound?
That's the sound of the energy
left over from your punches
reverberating throughout the tower.
What?
You may want to consider this…
Ever heard of
the law of conservation?
Energy that is collected
will eventually be released.
I wonder where it's gonna go?
Holy shit…
Get down, Okuyasu!
What?!
Punch the tower
as much as you'd like,
all that energy is just going to go
around and around
and come right back to you.
Strike it, and you'll enjoy
a knuckle sandwich.
Cut it, and you'll need
a few bandaids.
Just think about it.
No matter how powerful or how
amazing one's abilities may be,
this tower cannot be destroyed!
Okuyasu!
I'm starting to worry, Josuke…
I didn't manage to dodge it.
It hollowed out a hole in my side.
Guess I should've warned you, huh…
I bet you guys are thinking that if
you manage to defeat me,
the user, you have a way out.
But that's just another pipe dream.
Remember, this Stand exists
independent of me.
Even if I drop dead,
this tower will likely continue
snaring victims forever.
That's Superfly's specialty.
Josuke…
Forever?
Don't look so serious.
Just find someone else to take
your place, Josuke Higashikata.
One person goes in,
and one person goes out.
Just trap some poor fool
and get yourself out.
It's kinda like
that card game Old Maid.
Actually,
it's a lot like human society.
Just hand over the old maid
to someone else.
Don't you agree?
Pulling someone else in
will certainly help Josuke.
Huh?
What?
Who better to go back than you…
To the tower's realm…
you shall return.
You…
Mikitaka! When did you…
What are you?
How are you a power line?
When did you get there?
What kind of power is this?
Kind of you to ask.
I am in fact an alien.
What?
Now that's what I call
being of assistance!
You must act now.
Please exit the confines
of the tower, Mr. Josuke.
Y-You bastard!
You freak in rock, Mikitaka!
Josuke, get out of there now.
Get out from under the tower!
R-Right…
Hell yeah!
You bastard! What the hell?!
The guy in the photograph
never mentioned
Josuke had any ally like you!
Being an alien, I have no knowledge
of this so-called Old Maid game,
but tricking Josuke and suddenly
telling him he is trapped forever…
appears to me a lot like
an adult beating a child
at a New Year's card game
by cheating.
That is why you should be the
one to remain within the tower.
Here is where you will remain.
You know,
living all this time up here
has given me
these really thick calluses.
They also hold a lot of stuff.
Die dickhead!
You seem to assume that what's
in your hand is a part of me,
but I'm afraid
that's a misconception.
That is not me,
but the power line
you were hanging onto before.
He did it!
All right!
Now get yourself to the top
and get over here, Mikitaka!
After so long, you happened to
step into my tower's realm.
You really think
I'd let you just walk away?
You're looking at a man who's
spent every moment of every day
thinking about escaping this tower!
Did you forget my warning?
This tower will return
any attack back onto the attacker.
That wire is also
a part of this tower!
I severed the line so that
the opening would face you.
Is this the end for me?
M-Mikitaka!
Get your ass out of there now!
I can heal that wound!
Nope, he's staying right here.
I get to leave!
Direction and angle, check.
If you strike it,
it'll strike back.
Mikitaka!
Y-You sick bastard!
You definitely made escaping
a little bit tougher,
but that's all behind me now.
I would guess prying
those suckers out will hurt a bit,
but you'll have all the time
in the world later to heal.
Some of the plants down there
are medicinal, you know.
Evil bastard!
You think you can get away
just cause you stepped
outside the tower?
I'll chase your deceitful ass
to the ends of the earth.
Of course I can get away,
you silly.
You still haven't uncovered
Yoshikage Kira's whereabouts,
am I right?
JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:42 AM
Who is this? I've never seen him
before in my life.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:14 AM
JULY 15TH (THURS) 10:38 AM
I'll figure out who he is…
I know it.
EPISODE 32
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 2